Bien. Aquí voy.
Concéntrate. Velocidad.
Soy veloz.
Un ganador. 42 perdedores.
Yo desayuno perdedores.
Desayuno...
Tal vez debí desayunar. Un desayunito estaría bien.
No, no, no, no, no, concéntrate.
Velocidad.
Soy más que rápido, más que veloz.
Soy un rayo.
- Oye Rayo, ¿listo?
Claro que sí.
El Rayo está listo.
I'm American made, Bud Light, Chevrolet
My mama taught me wrong from right
I was born in the South
Sometimes I have a big mouth
When I see something that I don't like
I gotta say it
We been driving this road
For a mightily long time
Payin' no mind to the signs
Well, this neighborhood's changed
It's all been rearranged
We left that change somewhere behind